

HELLO I'M ELVIS MUGISHA

l am a talented, ambitious and hardworking young man who is a team player but can also work independently

Confident in working with various computer systems and software configuration processes. Comfortable in working in fast-paced environment and delivering exceptional results in a timely manner

Experienced Front-End and Back-End Developer with excellent attention to detail and problemsolving skills

Proven experience with Python. Proficient in web development techniques and creating web applications such as Python Django, JavaScript, CSS, HTML and MySQL.

Familiar with Linux and GitHub

Applying For Software Developer Role

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, Diango Linux and Mac • • 0 0 0 0 0 0 MySQL and SQL PHP, JavaScript HTML Windows **CSS** Debugging • • • • • • •

EXPERIENCE

Innov8 Incubator program

Feb 2022 - April 2022 Rwanda

A.S.S Partners-Itd

Sept 2021-Nov 2021 Rwanda, Kigali

Personal Project

March 2022-April 2022 Rwanda

EDUCATION

Ines Ruhengeri

Sept 2018 - Dec 2021 Musanze, Rwanda

St Mathieu Busasamana

Feb 2017 - Nov 2017 Rubavu, Rwanda

E.S.Gisenvi Jan 2015 - Feb 2017 Rubavu, Rwanda

Teck lead

As the teck lead, I led the pod of 6 team members to evaluate the needs of store managers in Rwanda conducted 25 interviews and collaborated with UX lead to design prototypes. As a result, the proposed solution was validated and is on the roadmap to be implemented as a MVP application

Software developer intern

For the time I spent there at ASS partners Itd I worked on so many things. Some of them are, stand-up meeting like every day. And I contribute in so many things too, Updating the ASS Partner's Database, Updating and Testing functionality of the existing systems. And I was in a Team who has a huge project of developing a Software API based application for Web, Android and IOS

VisionArchitects Website

A minimalistic website aimed to perfection ,the goal of creating this website was to help visionarchitect to have a place where they can add their project so that people can see their work and contact them through the website, make comments to their work and even testify about their excellent work.

Bachelor Degree in Software Engineering

High School Diploma in Math-Chemistry & Biology

High School Diploma in Math-Chemistry & Biology

PORTFOLIO

https://elvismugisha.github.io/

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH •••••• FRENCH KINYARWANDA

HOBBIES & INTEREST



Movies



Travelling



Praying



Learning new things

LEARN MORE ABOUT ME



mugishaelvis104@gmail.com



In LinkedIn: /elvis-mugisha



+250780527973